CURRICULUM VITAE - LUKAS ROSENBERGER

CONTACT DATA:

Address: Mühlweg 10

9560 Feldkirchen

Austria

Telephone: +43664 1644190

Email: lukas.rosenberger@hotmail.com

Portfolio: http://mr-rossi.github.io/



PERSONAL SUMMARY:

Lukas Rosenberger is a Computer Science student, currently in his 3rd semester at the University of Applied Sciences Salzburg. He is studying MultiMediaTechnology, a modern blend of Computer Science and Media Technologies with a major focus on Video Game Engineering and Computer Vision. Lukas is a passionate programmer who enjoys acquiring new knowledge and likes to keep up with the newest developments, thinking about how they could improve current technology.

technology.

EDUCATION:

09/2014 - 07/2017 UNIVERSITY OF APPLIED SCIENCES SALZBURG

MultiMediaTechnology

09/2008 - 07/2013 SECONDARY TECHNICAL VOCATIONAL COLLEGE AND INSTITUTE FOR

RESEARCH AND TECHNOLOGY VILLACHDepartment for Computer Sciences

Matura (with diploma)

Diploma: "SAP-Transaktionen vom Smartphone aus" (SAP transactions

on smartphones)

WORK EXPERIENCE:

2015 SWITCH-APP

University of Natural Resources and Life Sciences, Vienna

07/2013 - 01/2014 **MILITARY SERVICE**

Hensel-Kaserne, Villach

07/2012 - 08/2012 **Internship + Diploma**

Supanz GmbH

Developing a mobile app to execute transactions in SAP systems.

2009 - 2011 **Various Internships**

CURRENT EXPERTISE:

Proficient in C++, C#, Java HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP; SQL, Oracle, SAP+ABAP;

Modern OpenGL, including Shader Programming in GLSL

Computer Vision

Basic 3D-modeling in Maya Linear Algebra and Statistics Software Architecture and Design Algorithms and Datastructures

Video Game Engineering

Knowledge of Web Based Technologies including HTML and CSS,

Databases, node.js

PERSONAL:

Nationality: Austrian

Languages: German (native),

English (First Certificate in English Grade A - C1),

Italian (basics)

Hobbies: 3D printing, Video Games, Pen&Paper RPGs

PERSONAL STATEMENT:

As an avid gamer and technology geek getting to study

MultiMediaTechnology at the University of Applied Science

MultiMediaTechnology at the University of Applied Sciences Salzburg is the perfect way of extending my personal hobbies into my future work

life.

I'm looking forward to putting the knowledge I will have acquired by summer 2016 into practice by gaining actual video game industry experience for the first time.

I enjoy developing solutions to difficult problems and finding ways to

improve on existing concepts. I can easily get excited about almost any kind of game project and will try to do everything possible to make games a great experience.

My focus is on game developme

My focus is on game development and game design and I'm always trying to stay on top of new developments in those topics.

Currently I have developed 3 games, which you can find on my website http://mr-rossi.github.io/. By the time I start my Internship I will have developed a third game using Unity3D, so I will have a good insight into modern video game development.